{
    "id": "554720873a894004bdda8a31cf81781f",
    "title": "All or every: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a2c2f59952364266b5f3289ebdbc9a06",
            "title": "All And Every Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………………………. child needs love.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "Every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have written to ……………………………… my friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have written to ……………………………… friend I have.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My family …………………………….. work in education.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not …………………………….. birds can sing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… person made his or her own travel arrangements.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Every",
                        "All"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I see her ………………………….. few days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "all"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a meeting ……………………………… six weeks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "all"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have cleaned ……………………………. the rooms except the bathroom.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You don’t see tigers ……………………………… day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}